http://www.oldglory.com/pages/privacy-policy

Shopping Cart
"Close Cart"
Browse
Close menu
Music
See More
"Close Cart"
Classic Rock
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
NFL
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
Dale Earnhardt Jr.
See More
"Close Cart"
TV Shows
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
Clothing Lines
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
Pop Culture
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
Hockey
Mixed Martial Arts (MMA)
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
See More
"Close Cart"
Page
WELCOME TO OLDGLORY.COM (THE "SITE").
We understand that privacy online is important to users of our Site, especially when conducting business. This statement governs our privacy policies with respect to those users of the Site ("Visitors") who visit without transacting business and Visitors who register to transact business on the Site and make use of the various services offered by OldGlory.com (collectively, "Services") ("Authorized Customers").
PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION
Refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains, including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, fax number, email address, financial profiles, social security number, and credit card information. Personally, Identifiable Information does not include information that is collected anonymously (that is, without identification of the individual user) or demographic information not connected to an identified individual.
WHAT PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION IS COLLECTED?
We may collect basic user profile information from all of our Visitors. We collect the following additional information from our Authorized Customers: the names, addresses, phone numbers and email addresses of Authorized Customers, and the nature and size of the products that the Authorized Customer intends to purchase.
WHAT ARE ORGANIZATIONS COLLECTING THE INFORMATION?
In addition to our direct collection of information, our financial service vendors (such as credit card companies and banks) may collect this information from our Visitors and Authorized Customers. We ask them to disclose how they use personal information provided to them from Visitors and Authorized Customers. These third parties are intermediaries that act solely as links in the distribution chain and do not store, retain, or use the information given to them.
HOW DOES THE SITE USE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION?
We use Personally Identifiable Information to customize the Site, to make appropriate service offerings, and to fulfill buying and selling requests on the Site. We may email Visitors and Authorized Customers about research or purchase and selling opportunities on the Site or information related to the subject matter of the Site. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to contact Visitors and Authorized Customers in response to specific inquiries, or to provide the requested information.
WITH WHOM MAY THE INFORMATION MAY BE SHARED?
We may share aggregated information about our Visitors, including the demographics of our Visitors and Authorized Customers, with our affiliated agencies and third party vendors. We also offer the opportunity to "opt out" of receiving information or being contacted by us or by any agency acting on our behalf.
HOW IS PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION STORED?
Personally Identifiable Information collected by OldGlory.com is securely stored and is not accessible to third parties or employees of OldGlory.com except for use as indicated above.
WHAT ARE CHOICES AVAILABLE TO VISITORS REGARDING COLLECTION, USE, AND DISTRIBUTION OF THE INFORMATION?
Visitors and Authorized Customers may opt out of receiving unsolicited information from or being contacted by us and/or our vendors and affiliated agencies by responding to emails as instructed, or by contacting us at customerservice@oldglory.com
ARE COOKIES USED ON THE SITE?
Cookies are used for a variety of reasons. We use Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of our Visitors and the services they select. We also use Cookies for security purposes to protect our Authorized Customers.
HOW DOES OLDGLORY.COM USE LOGIN INFORMATION?
OldGlory.com uses login information, including, but not limited to, IP addresses, ISPs, and browser types, to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user's movement and use, and gather broad demographic information.
WHAT PARTNERS OR SERVICE PROVIDERS HAVE ACCESS TO PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION FROM VISITORS AND/OR AUTHORIZED CUSTOMERS ON THE SITE?
OldGlory.com has entered into and will continue to enter into affiliations with vendors. Such vendors may have access to certain Personally Identifiable Information on an aggregated basis in the course of providing services to OldGlory.com. Such vendors must meet the requirements of our privacy policy.
DISCLOSURE OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION TO COMPLY WITH LAW.
We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information in order to comply with a court order or subpoena or a request from a law enforcement agency to release information. We will also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when reasonably necessary to protect the safety of our Visitors and Authorized Customers.
HOW DOES THE SITE KEEP PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION SECURE?
All of our employees are familiar with our security policy and practices. The Personally Identifiable Information of our Visitors and Authorized Customers is only accessible to a limited number of qualified employees who are given a password in order to gain access to the information. We audit our security systems and processes on a regular basis. Sensitive information, such as credit card numbers or social security numbers, is protected by encryption protocols in place to protect information sent over the Internet. While we take commercially reasonable and advanced measures to maintain a secure site, electronic communications and databases are theoretically subject to errors, tampering, and break-ins. We cannot guarantee or warrant that such events will never take place but we take every prudent measure to guard against them. We will not be liable to Visitors or Authorized Customers for any such occurrences.
HOW CAN VISITORS CORRECT ANY INACCURACIES IN PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION?
Visitors and Authorized Customers may contact us to update Personally Identifiable Information about them or to correct any inaccuracies by emailing us at customerservice@oldglory.com.
CAN A VISITOR DELETE OR DEACTIVATE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION COLLECTED BY THE SITE?
We provide Visitors and Authorized Customers with a mechanism to delete/deactivate Personally Identifiable Information from the Site's database by contacting customerservice@oldglory.com. However, because of backups and records of deletions, it may be impossible to delete a Visitor's entry without retaining some residual information. An individual who requests to have Personally Identifiable Information deactivated will have this information functionally deleted, and we will not sell, transfer, or use Personally Identifiable Information relating to that individual in any way moving forward.
WHAT HAPPENS IF THE PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES?
We will let our Visitors and Authorized Customers know about changes to our privacy policy by posting such changes on the Site. However, if we are changing our privacy policy in a manner that might cause disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information that a Visitor or Authorized Customer has previously requested not be disclosed, we will contact such Visitor or Authorized Customer to allow such Visitor or Authorized Customer to prevent such disclosure.
LINKS:
This website may contain links to other websites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another website. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours.
Our Address:
